huggies.com.au 2019-09-05

# Kimberly-Clark Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

Kimberly-Clark Australia Pty Limited (" **KCA** ") respects and is committed to upholding your rights to privacy protection under the Australian Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (including the Australian Privacy Principles) and the New Zealand Privacy Act 1993 (including the Information Privacy Principles).  KCA will comply with the Australian Privacy Principles and the Information Privacy Principles which regulate the collection, use, disclosure and handling of personal information.

Personal information is information or an opinion about an identified individual, or an individual who is reasonably identifiable:

  * whether the information or opinion is true or not; and
  * whether the information or opinion is recorded in a material form or not.

This privacy policy (the “ **Policy** ”) details the practices that we have adopted to protect your privacy, so that you can feel confident about how we manage the personal and sensitive information you entrust to us.

By using our websites or otherwise providing us with personal information (including sensitive information), you consent to us collecting, using, disclosing and/or transferring (including cross-border transfer) that information in accordance with this Policy.

Please ensure that you read this Policy before submitting your information to us. Before providing personal information to us relating to other persons, you must obtain their consent and notify them of the location of this Policy.

**What kinds of personal information will we collect, and why do we collect it?**

KCA will collect and hold personal information that is necessary for our business functions and activities, or to comply with our legal obligations. Personal information may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, date of birth, postal address or social media account ID.

Because of the nature of our products, we may also collect sensitive information about you, including information concerning your health or medical condition.

**How do we collect your personal information?**

We collect personal information in a number of ways, including information that you provide to us:

  * through your use of our websites;
  * when you request a sample, make an enquiry, or provide feedback about a KCA product;
  * when you make a payment to us or our carefully selected partners;
  * when you submit a rating or user review about a KCA product;
  * when you participate in KCA promotions, events or market research; and
  * when you apply for employment with KCA.

In addition, there will be circumstances where we obtain your personal information from other sources, such as joint marketing partners, social media platforms or persons with whom you are connected on social media platforms.

_**Cookies and passive information collection**_

Like many companies, we sometimes use "cookie" technology or other automated means on our websites to collect certain information about you, your computer or other device through which you access our websites. These cookies are stored on your device by your browser to save your preferences while you are visiting a particular site. When you log in, the cookie tells us whether you have visited us before or are a new visitor, and it enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie does not obtain any personal information about you or provide us with any way to contact you. We use cookies to help us to identify, customise and deliver content such as advertisements, promotions or offerings of greatest interest to you, gather statistical information and better understand individual use.  In certain cases, we share this information with third parties to assist us in this process. If you choose, you may set your browser to reject cookies or you can manually delete individual or all of the cookies on your computer by following your browser’s help file directions. However, if you do not enable cookies to be received by your web browser, you may have trouble accessing some of the pages and certain features on our websites.

Pixel tags, web beacons, clear GIFs and similar technologies may also be used by us or our third party service providers to measure the success of marketing campaigns and compile statistics about site usage.  A web beacon is an electronic file on a Web page that allows us to count and recognise users who have visited that page. Among other things, a web beacon can be used in HTML-formatted email to determine responses to our communications and measure their effectiveness (e.g. if you get an email from us and click on a link in that email to go to our website). You can generally avoid web beacons in email by turning off HTML display and displaying only the text portion of your email.

Furthermore, and as is common practice, we may identify and compile information concerning your IP address (a number automatically assigned to your computer by your internet service provider) which helps us to calculate site usage levels, diagnose technical problems and administer our websites.

**What will we do with your personal information?**

Your personal information will be collected, held, used and disclosed by us in accordance with this Policy and applicable privacy laws.  We may disclose or use your personal information for the purpose for which we collected it, as well as for related purposes where you would reasonably expect us to do so. This may include (but is not limited to) the following:

  * to respond to your inquiries or feedback and to fulfil your requests;
  * to process rewards, donations, prizes, or sample requests;
  * to provide you with updates, announcements and details of promotional activities concerning any KCA brands, as well as non-KCA brands which we believe may be of interest to you (based on your browsing history);
  * to enable you to participate in social sharing, including live social media feeds and blogs;
  * for our business purposes, including quality assurance,  market research, developing and improving our products, enhancing our sites, identifying usage trends and measuring customer satisfaction;
  * in dealing with our third party service providers that provide services such as advertising, web hosting and moderating, e-mail and direct mail delivery and IT services and fulfilment houses;
  * where the law requires, or permits, us to do so, including sharing your information with government entities, or third parties in response to subpoenas, court orders, other legal process, or as we believe is necessary to exercise our legal rights, to defend against legal claims that have been brought against us, or to defend against possible legal claims that we determine in our sole discretion might be brought against us; and
  * for other purposes disclosed to you when we collect your information.

In addition:

  * we may decide to allow users of our websites and social media pages to share comments, postings, testimonials (including ratings or reviews), or other information. If you choose to submit such information to us, the information that you submit may be available generally to the public. Information that you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them; and
  * circumstances may also arise where KCA decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganise its business. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual buyers or sellers. It is our practice to seek appropriate protection for the disclosure of such information in these types of transactions.

You may restrict the use of your personal information at any time by using the unsubscribe mechanism that we include in our communications with you.

We will take all reasonable steps to maintain the security and integrity of your personal information including through the use of access passwords, firewalls and requiring that our partners protect your personal information.

We may share your personal information with certain third parties (as described below). If we do share your personal information with third parties, we will use our best endeavours to ensure that they observe and adhere to the terms of this Policy.

_**How we share your personal information**_

We may share your personal information between different departments of KCA, across different brands of KCA, with KCA group of companies (including our parent company, subsidiaries and global affiliates) and with third parties such as (but not limited to) marketing agencies who assist us with our promotional, marketing and research activities.  We may also give your information including your name, e-mail, telephone number or postal addresses to a fulfilment house or distributor of our products in order to carry out your requests.

We may share your personal information with our carefully selected partners when we believe their products or services may interest you. You may restrict such use of your personal information at any time by using the opt-out mechanism that we include in our communications with you. Our partners are prohibited from using your personal information for purposes other than presenting relevant offers and programs, and they are required to maintain your personal information in confidence.

We may share your personal information with companies or individuals that provide us with services. These services may include, among other things, helping us to provide services that you request, to create or maintain our databases, to research and analyse the people who request products, services, or information from us, to prepare and distribute communications, or to respond to inquiries.

We participate in interest-based (on-line behaviour) advertising. This means that a third party may use technology, such as a cookie on your browser or a web beacon, to identify you on our website so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interest. You may see advertising on our website tailored to how you browse or shop, or you may see advertising for our products on other websites based on your browsing behaviour across websites.

We may share non-personal information with other third parties that are not described above. When we do so we may aggregate or de-identify the information so that a third party would not be likely to link data to you, your computer, or your device. Aggregation means that we combine the non-personal information of numerous people together so that the data does not relate to any one person. De-identify means that we attempt to remove or change certain pieces of information that might be used to link data to a particular person.

KCA will use the details you provide to us, including feedback given to our Consumer Engagement Team (whether by e-mail, telephone, letter or fax) in order to provide you with the information, services and products necessary to satisfy your customer inquiry or complaint. We may also from time to time provide details of a serious complaint to the relevant supervisory government body (such as the Australian Competition and Consumer Commission and the Therapeutic Goods Administration) in order to meet our legal obligations and in the interests of public safety. By submitting feedback, you consent to our use and disclosure of your personal and sensitive information in this way.

_**Overseas disclosure of your personal information**_

Your personal information may be disclosed to KCA’s affiliate companies or third party service providers located outside of Australia or New Zealand.  It is likely that those overseas recipients will be located in the United States of America, Thailand, Vietnam, the United Kingdom, Czech Republic, India, Korea or Malaysia, though this list will change from time to time.  If you provide your personal information to us in accordance with this Policy, you are taken to consent to the disclosure of your personal information to overseas recipients.  As a result of your consent, Australian Privacy Principle 8.1 will not apply to the disclosure.  Whilst we will make every reasonable effort to ensure that recipients of your information protect your personal information, we will not be obliged to ensure that overseas recipients comply with the Australian Privacy Principles or New Zealand Information Privacy Principles (as relevant).

_**Information collected through employment applications**_

In processing applications for employment, KCA collects resumes, references, certificates of graduation and qualification and other personal information about candidates. We may also provide your application to a recruitment agency or contractor that may assist in reviewing applications we receive.

Letters and resumes sent to KCA as part of an application for an advertised position, or sent to ascertain whether any positions are available, will be used to match applicants with available opportunities. If we consider that your application may be suitable to our current requirements, we, or a party acting on our behalf, will notify you and may also contact persons nominated by you as referees and ask them questions in relation to you. If your application is not suitable for our current requirements, but we feel that there may be a position for you in the future, we may keep a record of your application and contact you again if a suitable position becomes available. Please advise us if you prefer that we do not retain your information for this purpose.

**Links and third parties**

This Policy does not cover, and we are not responsible for the practices of third parties, including any third parties that operate a website accessed through a link that appears on a KCA website. This includes any social media platforms to which you post content related to our products.

**How to access and correct your personal information or make a complaint**

If you would like to review, correct, update or delete the personal information that we hold concerning you, or if have any questions or complaints concerning a possible breach of the Australian Privacy Principles or the New Zealand Information Privacy Principles please contact our Privacy Officer:

**Mail** : The Privacy Officer, Kimberly-Clark Australia, 52 Alfred St, Milsons Point NSW 2061, Australia  
 **Phone** : (Australia):  +61 (0)2 9963 8888  
 **Phone** : (New Zealand):  \+ 64 (0)9 523 5970  
 **E-mail** : privacykca@kcc.com

We will refer any complaints to our Privacy Officer to investigate and to determine the steps we will take to resolve the complaint.  We aim to acknowledge receipt of your complaint within 5 working days, and to address the complaint within 15 working days.  We may also request information from you to help us with our investigation.

**Updates to this Policy**

We may change this Policy from time to time.  The date on which the Policy was last updated is noted at the top of this page.  Any changes to the Policy are effective from posting the revised Policy on this website.
